[{"answer": "Five o'clock", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You're not late", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Of course we'll hit traffic. It's rush hour", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "There is no other way in that place. Everybody goes every way all the time. my friend But it's Saturday. my friend got the picnic and burger traffic. GEORGE I always get myself in this position. Can't be on time. Gotta rush. my friend STOPS AND LOOKS AROUND", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Did I need that pointed out for me? What is that going to do for me? How does that help me, to see her? I'm trying to live my life. Don't show me that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, right. I'll just go up and say,", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Why be uncomfortable if you don't have to? It's organic", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Uh huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Unbelievable, I'm never gonna get out of here. The guy goes to pee, he never comes back. It's like a science fiction story", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh now you're gonna go? ELAINE I'll be back in five minutes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh what's the difference? We'll all be dead eventually", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah, it bothers me. Doesn't it bother you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Not at all", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I once saw this thing on T.V. with people who are terminally ill. And they all believed the secret of life is just to live every moment", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And now he's gone. I'm sure he's looking for the car. Five minutes, that's all. I just want to find him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "But why? Why can't you do it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That's right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "He was a wrestler. He would grab hold of someone's stomach and just squeeze it until they gave", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "So go", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So what do you want me to do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Garage.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That is an opening", "qsentId": 24}]